...the time to start worrying about the future of our jobs has arrived.
On March 18th, NVIDIA unveiled the Blackwell B200 Tensor Core chip.
The company's most powerful single chip GPU with 208 billion transistors.
NVIDIA claims it can reduce AI inference operating costs such as running chat GPT and energy
consumption by up to 25 times compared to the H100,
a chip they put into production two years ago.
The company also unveiled the GB200, a super chip that combines the B200 chips and the
Grace CPU for even more performance.
The Blackwell platform will allow the training of trillion parameter AI models that will
make today's generative AI models look rudimentary in comparison.
All in all...